It appears that village is indeed
amassing military might
and planning something foul!
They may be convincing
Flowrem to stay there
so that they can use her as
a hostage if they need to!
We should begin gathering
our troops at once, Princess!
I understand.
We must defeat that village
and save Flowrem.
Farming Life in Another World
Masshiro hikari no naka me o samashite
hajimatteiku sutoorii
Fumidasu atarashii sekai donna hana o sakaseyou?
Kumori sora datte mizutamari de yogoretatte
Bokura wa susumu
Souzou mo shinai mirai ga matteiru kitto
Deatte deatte tsunagatteku
Waraeba mawari mo egao ni naru
Chiisana tane maite sodateyou
Yagate ookina hana ni naru
Koukai ya shippai wa kate ni shite
Karafuru na shiawase de afureru youni
Bokura te o toriatte wakeatte
Sekaijuu ni hirogatteike Flower Ring
I'm sorry to bother you
while you're looking busy.
I'm not just looking busy, I am busy.
I've been put in charge of
the village's accounting.
That aside, what brings you here so late?
The thing is, our princess
is gathering troops
and preparing to go on
a military campaign.
Our princess is doing what?
Demon Lord Galgardo's Daughter
Princess Yuri
Why would she do something that absurd?
While you've been gone,
some of her followers
have taken the opportunity
to fill her head with half-truths.
And by followers, you mean...
The second daughter of the Gritch family,
Gritch Family
Second Daughter
Rosalind
the fourth daughter of the Bugal family,
Bugal Family
Fourth Daughter
Klakkase
and the second daughter of
the Mamonrose family.
Mamonrose Family
Second Daughter
Roaju
Aren't those simpletons the
trio of politically powerful idiots?!
So where exactly are they
planning to attack?
This village.
What are they eating that's giving them
such ridiculous ideas?!
Besides, I've given them
plenty of reports, haven't I?!
They should know how ridiculously
powerful this village is!
I think the reports were so ridiculous
that they started to seem unrealistic.
I tried to have the demon lord
put a stop to this,
but he's far too soft on his daughter.
Then do you think it's best
if I go convince them to stop?
They'd be expecting that.
It would cause them to view you as
an enemy of the Demonic Kingdom.
Then what should I do?
I just need you to stop their invasion...
By the way, when are they mobilizing?
Tomorrow.
Tomorrow?!
Their forces number 300 men.
I was thinking that maybe if we asked someone
from this village to rout their forces,
they'd give up and go home...
Sure.
Especially them
However, if we're careless about
which villagers find out about this...
it will likely end with the violent
destruction of the Demonic Kingdom.
That would be a problem.
So basically, I just need to show them
the difference in military might
without actually mobilizing
the village's forces, right?
P-please, spare our lives!
Have mercy!
Are we done already?
Yes!
They're really going to give us
ten boxes of apples just for this?
Do you think maybe we should
punish them just a little more?
Uh...
So who are those girls that have been
standing there frozen solid?
They're from the Demonic Kingdom,
and they'd like to move here.
They've had a complete change of heart and
are all ready to work themselves to death-
I mean, they're ready to work like
their lives depend on it.
Um, okay...
But still,
they kind of seem like they've given up.
Almost like they've accepted that
their lives are over, or something.
They'll be fine.
They're all acquaintances of mine,
so for the time being
I plan to have them working for me.
In the event that they do anything
to harm the village,
please don't hesitate to have them
disposed of. I won't mind at all.
That sounded scary.
Now that that's out of the way...
Who's that other girl over there?
She's here to observe for a while.
I'd like to show her how things work
here in the village.
M-my name is Yuri.
Apparently, she was worried about
my living conditions here in our village.
You don't need to give her
any special treatment.
Please put her to work with the
understanding that she'll be gone soon.
How does she expect me to do that?
Okay, you can show them around town.
Thank you! Just leave it to me!
Listen up.
If you all put in some honest work here,
your transgressions against
the village will be forgiven.
That said, I think in the interest of keeping
this little incident a secret from
the rest of the villagers,
it would be wise of you all
not to divulge your identities.
In other words, Princess...
Yes?
You won't receive any
special treatment here.
As long as you're in this village,
you'll just be plain old Yuri.
That won't be a problem.
It's been a long time
since I've been called by my name.
Now then, let's get started with
our tour of the village!
So these fruits are turned into alcohol?
These plants grow from inside the water?
This contraption moves not with magic,
but with the power of water?
Who are you?
Oh my!
Look how fluffy you are! So fluffy!
Hey, that tickles!
These are apples, right?
I had no idea they grew on trees like this.
Oh, do we have visitors?
I've never eaten apples
except for at parties at the castle.
I ate them every day at home.
At my house, we used to have the merchants
search for them and buy them up,
even when they were in short supply.
Are those girls nobles or something?
Y-yeah, something like that...
If we can take over this village,
it'll be the biggest money maker
for our kingdom.
Dispose!
N-never mind, it's nothing!
Nice to meet you!
I'm Lastismoon of the dragons.
Please call me Lasty!
Nice to meet you, Lasty.
She's awfully cute for a dragon.
I know we were forced to stay here,
but it's still absurd that nobles
of the Demonic Kingdom
are living in the middle of nowhere like this.
We'll be the laughingstock of
the country when we return.
Let's wait for a chance and then escape.
Have you learned your lesson?
Yes!
We promise!
We'll work like our lives depend on it!
Just please don't dispose of us!
Looks like they're really working hard.
They're actually a big help.
Now I can split up the mountain of
office work I had to deal with.
I'll be happy if I can keep them
working like this as part of the town hall.
Now named: The Town Hall Girls
That's an inferno wolf, isn't it?
Is it alright to be petting it like that?
Yeah!
Even though a single inferno wolf
is said to be dangerous enough
to cause serious damage
and harm to any city it enters,
they're really cute when they're like this.
I'm supposed to... throw this?
Yeah, they love it.
Let's see...
Go!
I wonder if I'll get used to this.
Eventually.
This village really has been
nothing but surprises.
I can't believe a world like this exists
outside of the Demonic Kingdom.
I'm pretty sure this is
a very rare exception.
No, I was just very ignorant
of the outside world.
I tried to bring war and conflict to
such a wonderfully peaceful place.
Anyone who takes up arms
against this place
should expect to find themself on
the receiving end of a dragon's fire breath.
Indeed they should.
To be honest, I thought the intel
about dragons living in this village
was a lie meant to deceive us.
I warned everyone not to
get involved with this village.
The demon lord should have
warned you against it as well.
So why did you do it?
It's your fault.
Flowrem, you just vanished from
the Demonic Kingdom one day!
I heard that you'd become a hostage,
and I was worried about you!
Princess...
My name is Yuri!
Stop acting like we haven't been friends
since we were children!
You stopped talking to me
when you needed help,
and then before I knew it everything from you
was princess this and princess that!
You treated me like a stranger!
I'm sorry, Yuri.
I'll keep you in the loop from now on.
I know you will.
Yeah.
Now then, let's head back.
It's almost time to eat.
Okay.
This office work is really hard,
but the food here is great.
We don't have to worry about
any stressful political conflicts.
We can just relax here.
The baths heal my soul.
I was worried that they might
have trouble adjusting to life here.
They've already fully adapted.
Are these the new girls?
Yeah.
You've been at that height
all day, haven't you?
Yeah, my transformation magic
hasn't really been working.
Oh well, I'm sure it'll get better soon.
I see.
Farming Life...
in Another...
World.
I know, right?
It's Big Sis!
Let me help out with all the farm work, too!
She's going to do manual labor?!
That's work for commoners!
Please stop this, Princess!
Princess?
Huh? Wasn't that a secret?
Never mind!
Disposal.
Now then, I want you all
to join me and help!
Huh? But...
Our specialty is office work.
Don't worry, we'll show you how!
I learned a lot from you all
during my time here in this village.
I'm very grateful to everyone.
You're leaving already?
I'm sorry.
I promise to come visit.
Um, here.
Oh my.
They're made from the wheat
that we harvested together.
Thank you very much.
Flow.
Don't forget to come visit.
Yeah.
Thank you too, mayor.
Yeah. Safe travels.
By the way...
are you all not coming home?
There are still things
for us to learn in this village!
And there's still a ton of work to do!
We haven't repaid everyone's kindness yet!
Therefore, we must remain here.
Please stop eating
at least while you're talking.
We should depart now.
Okay.
I'll see you all again sometime, everyone.
It looks like she enjoyed her time here.
Yes.
Hey, Beezel.
It's about Yuri.
Ever since she returned to the castle,
she's seemed a bit different.
Yes...
It's like she's grown dignified
all of a sudden...
She looks so busy every day.
Even if I try to have a conversation with her,
she doesn't really make time for me.
It seems that the princess will begin to
take an interest in politics and
diplomacy before too long.
Daughters tend to grow into adults
before their parents realize it.
Adults?
Don't tell me...
she met a man?!
Who is he?!
I, the great demon lord Galgardo,
will tear him apart myself!
That attitude is going to make her
hate you one day.
What?!
More importantly, it's time for a meeting.
Let's go and show her
what a cool father you can be.
Okay, I get it.
Leave it to me.
A short while after Yuri left,
we began our pre-winter crop harvest
and this was the result...
When did all this happen?!
We harvested so much that this here
is just what wouldn't fit into storage.
I'm happy we had a good harvest, but still...
This is a lot more than we were expecting.
In that case,
would it be alright if we sent
some of the extra to my father?
Yeah, let's do it.
Can we send some to my parents, too?
That's fine by me, but who are your parents?
From my perspective,
they're Granddad and Grandmom.
Grandfather
Grandmother
My father lives in the northern continent,
while my mother lives in the south,
so it's going to be a bit out of the way.
They're dragons living in
the north and south?
Might they be the Emperor Dragon Doze,
and the Hurricane Dragon Raimaylen?
Emperor Dragon Doze
Hurricane Dragon Raimaylen
You're exaggerating!
Is that really what you guys call them?
I never imagined the dragons
were all connected like this.
Those are some pretty intense names.
First, Lasty stopped by Dryme's place to
drop off the food we were sharing with him.
And then she continued on to Shashato City
to drop off the crops we were sending there.
Apparently, Michael asked her
to exterminate a monster that had been
attacking the trade vessels.
Sure!
You're mine!
Hey, guess what!
I got to take some meat home as thanks
for taking care of that monster!
This is definitely that chanco stuff
you were talking about, mayor!
Concept Art
That means we're having
chanco hotpot tonight!
Chanco
Uh, okay...
Meanwhile, Hakuren headed north.
On her way back, she found some people
that wanted to move to our village.
I'm Ya, the leader of this group.
Dark elves?
Huh? We're referred to as mountain elves.
Um, that's my mistake.
Please forget about it.
They can all use fire,
and they're meat eaters, too.
I see.
Normally we live up in the mountains,
but as of late, it's become
harder for us to find food.
They seemed like they were
having some trouble,
so I thought things might be easier for them
if they came and lived here.
I understand.
What should we do?
I understand that no one really has
the leeway to help out strangers these days.
If we're causing you any trouble,
we'll leave right away.
No, that's not what I meant!
I was only trying to think up
a plan in a hurry.
We need to figure out where you'll sleep
until we build you a house,
and other stuff like that.
I was just thinking about who I'll have to
talk to so I can sort everything out.
Does that mean...
Yeah.
If you're okay with living here,
we're happy to have you.
Thank you so much!
We're fine sleeping on the ground here!
No, we can't have that.
And so, the group of mountain elves
became residents of our village.
Mountain Elves
At the very least,
we'll go catch food on our own!
After all, we're excellent hunters!
Trap
Improved Trap
I'm terribly sorry that we
couldn't be of more use to you.
A-are you okay?!
Isn't there something wrong
with this forest?
You think so, too?
If it's too much for you,
please don't hurt yourselves.
You're very kind, mayor.
What's that you're working on?
I was hoping it would be possible to
make some pottery in the village.
I see.
And now, we bake it after it's dry.
Huh?
It's vanished...
I guess the soil here just won't work.
We'll have to go look for clay somewhere.
Would you allow me the honor
of finding that for you?!
We come from the mountains,
and as such, we understand the earth
and what lies within it!
I see.
But isn't it dangerous
to go searching the area?
As long as I don't have to fight,
I'll be quite alright!
I'm confident in my ability to flee.
Just promise me you'll be careful.
A Short While Later...
Wow!
This is great! It's perfect!
I did my best!
I wonder if we can make
cups and plates and stuff.
Of course!
Just leave it to me!
They found another dungeon?
Yes. It's a different one
than where the lamia live.
Ya found the entrance to the new dungeon
up north near the mountains.
I'd like your permission to send
a survey party there.
What if it's dangerous?
That's one reason we need to
survey the area and learn more.
I see.
Just don't do anything too drastic.
I've got this!
We're heading off now.
While the survey team was off
investigating the dungeon,
the men's bathhouse was finally finished.
The dwarves and the lizardmen can use it,
and so can Dryme when he visits,
so I definitely didn't build this
so I could have it all to myself!
Yup.
Well, I don't mind how lively it is here.
Remember, you need to make sure
to wash yourselves before getting in here.
Okay!
What exactly do you all think
you're doing out here?
W-we thought this was
the women's bathhouse...
I won't get mad, so tell me the truth.
You're about to get
really mad at us, aren't you?
Well, um... we were hoping that maybe
we could wash the mayor's back for him.
We thought it could be a good chance
to get closer to him...
Listen up.
We're all the absolute lowest
ranking members in this village.
I told you this was a bad idea!
You can't expect to slip by everyone else
and sneak your way to the top.
I tried to stop this!
You can't expect to slip by everyone else
and sneak your way to the top.
Huh? Wha?!
You can't expect to slip by everyone else
and sneak your way to the top.
Huh? Wha?!
You know what'll happen
if you try something like that, right?
P-please, just don't let them
dispose of us!
This is your last warning.
Before long, the dungeon
survey party had returned.
What is it?
You're all here...
We should send an extermination party
to the dungeon up north!
Is something there a problem?
We confirmed the presence of
a blood viper inside.
Ah, that was the thing fighting the bear.
We absolutely must have its meat!
The survival of our clan
depends on us getting ahold of it!
Is it really that important?
Blood viper meat is said to be
extremely valuable.
Eating it makes your body
overflow with vitality,
and it improves husband-wife relations.
It's also said to bless you with children...
W-well, it's almost winter.
Let's talk it over with the whole village
before we set out to hunt it.
And so, autumn faded away
as winter began to approach.
Then one day...
I never thought I'd see you
of all people bedridden.
What a strange sight.
Are you okay?
I heard you weren't feeling well.
I'm fine. It's nothing serious.
I might have just caught a cold.
Isn't mixing up different kinds
of medicines your specialty?
I've never tried making a medicine
for myself before this.
Don't look at me like that.
It's just a little bit of nausea
and a slight fever.
I'm sure I'll be fine
if I rest for a little while.
I hope that's all it is.
This might be a long shot,
but have you found yourself
craving sour foods lately?
Now that you mention it,
I don't really have an appetite
but I'm still able to eat tomatoes and fruits.
Um, there was someone in Howling Village
who said the same thing.
Lulucy, have you really
not figured it out yet?
What is it?
And that person?
What happened to them?
Um...
We congratulated them on the baby.
What?!
Kisetsu no kaze fuwari yubisaki de sotto kanjiru
Sora ni ukabu kumo ni daisuki sagasou
Tokei no hari wa ima wa wasure
Shinkokyuu hitotsu shitemiyouyo
Nanairo no keshiki kokoro hibiku
Donna negai koto demo kanau ki ga suru
Kimi ga soba ni iru nara
Yume mitaina hibi o kuretan dayo
Atatakakute yasashii basho de
Itsumademo egao o miseteite
Next Time
Episode 11
Everyday Life, and the Progenitor